Hey Guy once again welcome back to CSC Head
2.0 welcome all of you once again
I am Ratej Mishra and you are watching
CAC Head here friends in this video we are going to
talk about when
you login then it
asks about KYC etc so what is it how will KYC be done
and how will the identity ID be made what is the
process so I will tell you step by step here
so let's start and you have to do it in the
same way as I will tell you
and your identity ID will be made
after that how do you have to do
insurance here so I will
show you all that process here so let's
go to the system and show you here
first you have to go to your CSC
portal here in the dashboard and there
you have to go to the insurance tab
like if you go to insurance then many
insurance portals will be
visible here so you have to
go to ADFC Egg here if you are not able to find it then let me
tell you that if you go
to any motor cans then you will find it there then
from there if you click here then the
ADAC dashboard will open here  After that
you have to click on CSC Connect here,
like when you click on CSC Connect, then here
you will see KYC ID please click,
so you have to click on this, click here,
as if you click on this, then here
you have to enter your full name on login,
after that enter mobile number and click on get OTP,
then OTP will be sent to your mobile number
and you have to enter that OTP here and
submit it, then proceed, so
as soon as you enter it here and
verify it by entering OTP, then
you have to enter PAN card here, so now see,
there is a KYC ID, identity
ID, if you do not have it, you will have to
create it, if you are coming for the first time then
click on add new, then you will have to enter PAN
card number here, enter PAN card,
after that enter date of birth and after that
proceed, if you want, you
can also do it here with Aadhar card, so I will say that
you should do it only by entering PAN card, so I will
enter it here, after that if we proceed further,
it will fill the data, a dialog box will
come, then you will have to click yes here, which is PAN  If the
name is there in the card, as it is, the same name will remain, then
you have to click on yes here,
after that you will have to enter your mother's name and father's name
here
and it will take your address from here,
after that you have to click on proceed here, so
let me do that too here,
you will fill the rest of the things here as per your own,
after that you have to
click on continue here, like if you
click on continue here, then you will have to
select your annual income here,
select the occupation and give some details
of the business here, if you have taken it then
select the lowest one,
what is there in the organization,
if you are government, private, public then you can do that,
otherwise you will choose other here,
after that if you have a
CSC center, then what can you do,
you have to write something here about
where you work, in other business,
so here you can write common service center,
okay, after that are you
politically exposed option is coming here, so
here  You have to say no, if you
are a politician then you will say yes, if you are not a
politician then you will say no and after that you will
click on proceed, then if I do it here then
see when I do it here then
some error is coming, actually I have
not selected the occupation here so
I will do that, then in occupation you will
select self employed here
because you have your own business, even if you are a
government employee then you
can select it, after that you have to click continue,
see your KYC will be
completed here and you will get the ID here,
after that you will
come here again on click here and click again, you will
enter the same thing, ID password and OTP
sorry I am doing ID password, you will
enter the name here and enter the OTP, after that
click on continue, then you will get an OTP
and you have to enter the OTP here and
submit it, then you will see here you will
get the identity ID, you will click on it, then a
message of thank you will come and what you have to do again, you will have to
come to HDFC and
click again  You have to do it here and
connect CSC, after that you
can do insurance of all your policies here, comprehensive, motor third party, from here, in
this way you can create your identity ID
and after creating the identity ID,
now you can go to the buy page of any insurance and
buy it there, meaning you
can do any insurance of anyone,
whatever option is available there, it was just a very
short video, so I hope you have
understood it here, if you liked the
video, please like, share and
subscribe, you have just taken CSC BA
and you have recently joined CSC, so
if you want to do business in a good way, then
keep subscribing to this channel
because I will tell you very good things
here, how you should work in CSC,
where are the advantages and disadvantages in CSC,
you will get all those things here,
so you
must subscribe to this channel and like this video
and watch every video that comes
so that you will
definitely get to learn something new in it because if
you do not watch new videos then  So what will happen is that there will be
some new schemes, if you watch them late then the
schemes get over, so if you
keep watching the videos regularly then you will benefit, so
come on guys, we will meet again
in the next video, if you have any doubt in your mind, any
question, then you can go to Ritesh 34 ID
or you can ask here in the comment,
so we will meet again in the next video, till then
take care,
bye